globexdesigns.com 2010-09-05

# Globex Designs, Inc. - Privacy Policy

This policy is effective as of January 12, 2010

## Globex Designs Privacy Policy

Privacy is very important on the Internet and at Globex Designs, Inc. we take all measures to ensure all our visitors' privacy is respected and protected. This policy applies to all pages under the control of Globex Designs, Inc. If you have any questions about this policy, please do not hesitate to contact us by visiting [the Contact Page](http://www.globexdesigns.com/contact.php "the Contact Page"). We would be happy to discuss any concerns or suggestion you may have.

We offer many services and products that require no registration, such as the Google Redesigned project. For other services such as our Client Center and the Forums we may collect the following types of information:

## The Information We Collect

**Information you provide** When you sign up for a new Globex Designs account we ask you for some personal information such as your name, email address and password. We do not collect or store any billing information such as credit cards, bank account numbers, or billing addresses. All transactions are done via third party services such as [PayPal](http://www.paypal.com/ "PayPal"). Those transactions are protected by the policies of our partners.

**Cookies** When you visit this site, we send several cookies (small files containing system information) to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends, such as which of our resources you found most useful. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some services may not work if your cookies are disabled.

**Log information** When you browse the site, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, IP address, browser, operating system, language and the date of your request. This information is strictly used for statistical use only in order to improve our website for all our users.

**Email communication** When you send in an inquery to our staff, we retain all email communication sent in order to respond to your requests in an efficient manner.

We never provide any of this gathered information to our affiliates, partners or any other third party website without clearly informing you of such actions beforehand.

## Google Redesigned

The [Google Redesigned](http://www.globexdesigns.com/gr "Google Redesigned") Firefox extension changes the look and feel of popular Google™ services.

The extension has no access to any data on any of your Google accounts. The only information the extension will check for is your current extension version and the versions of the extension styles (eg. Gmail Redesigned, Gcal Redesigned, etc) in order to ensure your styles are up-to-date. Google Redesigned is certified by Mozilla Add-ons editors who verify all Firefox extensions for security and stability.

The Google Redesigned code is available freely under the GPL OpenSource license.

## Terms of Use, Notices and Revisions

Your use of Globex Designs services, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our [Terms of Use](http://www.globexdesigns.com/terms.php "Terms of Use") and all of its dispute resolution provisions including arbitration, limitation on damages and choice of law. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use at any time. Non-material changes and clarifications will take effect immediately, and material changes will take effect within 30 days of their posting on this site. If we make changes, we will post them and will indicate at the top of this page the policy's new effective date. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or through notice on our home page. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.
